A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986, RG 37 FA1504
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986; 37; 327.55 Cubic Feet 857 containers
  - Clubs, 1982-1986; 6; 1.99 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
    - Woodstock Golf and Tennis Club - Finances (Box 113, Folder 1-3)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1982-1986; 7; 1.61 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - A-Z (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Bassett Hall (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Contributions (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Finances (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Carlisle H. Humelsine (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Printed Matter (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Abby A. Rockefeller Folk Art Center (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - DeWitt Wallace Decorative Art Gallery (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Hotel Properties, Inc. - A-Z (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Commercial Ventures, 1982-1986; 8; 3.89 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes and 1 legal box
    - Commercial Ventures - A-B (Box 116, Folder 2-3)
    - Commercial Ventures - C-L (Box 117, Folder 1-5)
    - Commercial Ventures - M-R (Box 118, Folder 1-4)
    - Commercial Ventures - S-Z (Box 119, Folder 1-2)
    - Archer-Daniels-Midland Company (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Catoctin Thoroughbred Partners (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Jojoba Developers, Inc. (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - West Bank Community Development Corporation (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Banking - A-Z (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - A (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - B-H (Box 121, Folder 1-4)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - I-S (Box 122, Folder 1-4)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - T-Z (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - American Business Consultants Corporation (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - Guinea Investment Forum (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - International Advisory Committee (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - International Advisory Committee (Box 124, Folder 1-2)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - Pahlavi, Mohammed Reza (Shah of Iran) - Newspaper Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - Works Of Art (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - Works Of Art - Art Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Banking - National Consumer Cooperative (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Conservation, 1982-1986; 9; 20.6 Cubic Feet 53 letter document boxes and 1 legal box
    - Conservation - A-Z, 1
      - Conservation - A-C (Box 125, Folder 2-3)
      - Conservation - D-G (Box 126, Folder 1-3)
      - Conservation - H-O (Box 127, Folder 1-4)
      - Conservation - P-Z (Box 128, Folder 1-3)
      - American Conservation Association (Box 128, Folder 4, Box 129, Folder 1)
      - American Environment, Inc. (Box 129, Folder 2)
      - American Environmental Safety Council (Box 129, Folder 3)
      - American Forestry Association (Box 129, Folder 4)
      - American Minor Breeds Conservancy (Box 129, Folder 5)
      - American Rivers Conservation Council (Box 129, Folder 6)
      - Appalachian Mountain Club (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - Citizens For A Better Environment (Box 130, Folder 2)
      - The Clean Water Fund (Box 130, Folder 3)
      - Conservation Foundation (Box 130, Folder 4)
      - Conservation Foundation - Printed Material (Box 130, Folder 5, Box 131, Folder 1)
      - Conservation Law Foundation Of New England, Inc. (Box 131, Folder 2-3)
      - Council On Environmental Alternatives (Box 131, Folder 4)
      - Cousteau Society, Inc. (Box 132, Folder 1)
      - Environment and Economy Project (Box 132, Folder 2)
      - Environmental Action Foundation - General (Box 132, Folder 3)
      - Environmental Action Foundation - Contributions (Box 132, Folder 4, Box 133, Folder 1)
      - Environmental Defense Fund (Box 133, Folder 2-3)
      - Environmental Defense Fund - Contributions (Box 133, Folder 4, Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Environmental and Energy Study Institute (Box 134, Folder 2)
      - Environmental Law Institute (Box 134, Folder 3)
      - Environmental Policy Institute, 1980-1986 (Box 134, Folder 4, Box 135, Folder 1-3)
      - Environmental Policy Institute - Contributions (Box 136, Folder 1-4)
      - Environmental Task Force (Box 136, Folder 5, Box 137, Folder 1-2)
      - The Farallones Institute (Box 137, Folder 3)
      - Friends Of The Earth Foundation (Box 137, Folder 4, Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Friends Of The Earth Foundation - Contributions (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Greater Yellowstone Coalition (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Island Resources Foundation (Box 138, Folder 4)
      - League Of Conservation Voters (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - National Audubon Society (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - National Audubon Society - Contributions (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - National Audubon Society - Garrison Diversion Reformulation Act Of 1986 (Box 140, Folder 1-2)
      - National Audubon Society - Printed Material (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - National Campaign Against Toxic Hazards (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - National Clean Air Fund (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - National Coalition Against The Misuse Of Pesticides (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - National Trust For Historic Preservation, 1977-1986 (Box 141, Folder 3-4, Box 142, Folder 1)
      - National Trust For Historic Preservation - Printed Material, 1977-1986 (Box 142, Folder 2-3)
      - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1979-1986 (Box 143, Folder 1-4, Box 144)
      - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc. - Contributions (Box 145, Folder 1)
        Conditions Governing Access
        Restricted - Living Rockefeller family members.
      - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc. Alida R. Dayton, 1982-1986 (Box 145, Folder 2-3)
      - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc. - Contributions - Sandra Ferry (Box 146, Folder 1-2)
      - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc. - Contributions - M/M Thomas Morgan (Box 146, Folder 3)
      - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc. - Contributions - Steven Rockefeller (Box 146, Folder 4)
      - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc. - Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller and Mary French Rockefeller (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc. - Printed Material (Box 147, Folder 2)
      - Natural Science for Youth Foundation (Box 147, Folder 3)
      - Nature Conservancy (Box 147, Folder 4)
      - Nature Conservancy - A-Z (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - Nature Conservancy, 1977-1986 (Box 148, Folder 2-3)
      - Nature Conservancy International Program (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - New York Zoological Society (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - New York Zoological Society - A-Z (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - New York Zoological Society - Annual Reports (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - New York Zoological Society - Board of Trustees (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - New York Zoological Society - Bronx Zoo (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - New York Zoological Society - Buddhist Perception of Nature - Nancy Nash (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - New York Zoological Society - Central Park Zoo (Prospect Park and Flushing Meadows Zoo) (Box 149, Folder 6)
      - New York Zoological Society - Contributions (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - New York Zoological Society - Finances (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - New York Zoological Society - Fund Raising (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - New York Zoological Society - Minutes-Meetings, 1982-1986 (Box 151, Folder 1-2, Box 152)
      - New York Zoological Society - Printed Material (Box 152, Folder 3, Box 153, Folder 1)
      - Northern Rockies Action Group (Box 153, Folder 2)
      - Northwest Conservation Act Coalition (Box 153, Folder 3)
      - On the Fate of the Earth (Box 153, Folder 4)
      - Open Space Institute (Box 153, Folder 5, Box 154, Folder 1)
      - Resources for the Future (Box 154, Folder 2)
      - Scientists Institute for Public Information (Box 154, Folder 3)
      - Shelburne Farms Resources, Inc. - Contributions (Box 154, Folder 4)
      - Shelburne Farms (Box 155, Folder 1)
      - Sierra Club Foundation - General (Box 155, Folder 2-3)
      - Sierra Club Foundation - Contributions (Box 156, Folder 1)
      - Sierra Club Foundation - Printed Matter (Box 156, Folder 2)
      - Southwest Research and Information Center (Box 156, Folder 3, Box 157, Folder 1)
      - Student Conservation Association, Inc. (Box 157, Folder 2)
      - Trust for Public Land (Box 157, Folder 3)
      - Urban Environment Conference, Inc., 1982-1984 (Box 157, Folder 4)
      - Wilderness Society (Box 158, Folder 1)
      - World Resources Institute (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - United States Government, 2
      - United States Government - A-Z (Box 158, Folder 3)
      - Citizen's Advisory Committee on Environmental Quality (Box 158, Folder 4)
      - Council on Environmental Quality (Box 158, Folder 5)
      - Department of the Interior (Box 158, Folder 6)
      - Department of the Interior - James Watt (Box 158, Folder 7)
      - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - A-Z (Box 159, Folder 1-2)
      - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - Eastern National Park and Monument Association (Box 159, Folder 3)
      - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Park Foundation (Box 159, Folder 4)
      - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks (Box 160, Folder 1)
      - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Great Smoky Mountain National Park (Box 160, Folder 2)
      - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - A-Z (Box 160, Folder 3-4)
      - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Wolf Trap Farm Park for the Performing Arts (Box 160, Folder 5)
      - Outdoor Recreation Policy Review Group, 1982-1985 (Box 161, Folder 1-4)
      - Outdoor Recreation Policy Review Group - Meetings (Box 162, Folder 1-2)
      - Outdoor Recreation Policy Review Group - Printed Material (Box 162, Folder 3)
      - Outdoor Recreation Policy Review Group - Reports (Box 162, Folder 4)
      - President's Commission on Americans Outdoors (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous States (Not New York), 3
      - Miscellaneous States - A-Z (Box 163, Folder 2-3)
      - Alaska (Box 163, Folder 4)
      - Maine (Box 164, Folder 1)
      - Maine - Maine Audubon Society (Box 164, Folder 2)
      - Maine - Natural Resources Council of Maine (Box 164, Folder 3)
      - Massachusetts (Box 164, Folder 4)
      - Oregon (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - Pennsylvania (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Texas (Box 174, Folder 2)
      - Texas - National Wildlife Research Center (Box 174, Folder 3-4)
      - Texas - National Wildlife Research Center - Clippings and Printed Matter (Box 175, Folder 1)
      - Texas - National Wildlife Research Center - Contributions (Box 175, Folder 2)
      - Vermont (Box 175, Folder 3)
      - Wyoming (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - New York State, 4
      - New York State - A-G (Box 164, Folder 5)
      - New York State - H-Z (Box 165, Folder 1-3)
      - Hudson River Foundation for Science and Environmental Research, 1982-1986 (Box 165, Folder 4-5, Box 166, Folder 1)
      - Hudson River Foundation for Science and Environmental Research - Meetings (Box 166, Folder 2)
      - Hudson River Valley Association (Box 166, Folder 3)
      - New York City (Box 167, Folder 1)
      - New York City - Central Park Conservancy (Box 167, Folder 2-3)
      - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - Contributions (Box 167, Folder 4)
      - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - Finances (Box 168, Folder 1)
      - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - Fundraising (Box 168, Folder 2)
      - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - Minutes-Meetings (Box 168, Folder 3)
      - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - Printed Matter (Box 168, Folder 4)
      - New York City - Council on the Environment of New York City (Box 169, Folder 1)
      - New York City - Department of Parks (Box 169, Folder 2)
      - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - A-Z (Box 169, Folder 3)
      - Pallisades Interstate Park Commission - Annual Reports, 1981-1986 (Box 169, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller State Park Preserve (Box 169, Folder 5, Box 170, Folder 1-3)
      - Rockefeller State Park Preserve - Dedication (Box 171, Folder 1)
      - Taconic State Park Commission Pocantico Hills, 1981 (Box 171, Folder 2)
      - Taconic State Park Commission - Rockwood Hall Park, 1972-1986 (Box 171, Folder 3-5)
      - Taconic State Park Commission - Rockwood Hall Park - Contributions, 1982-1986 (Box 171, Folder 6)
      - Taconic State Park Commission - Rockwood Hall Park - Clippings, Plans and Printed Matter, 1972-1976 (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Taconic State Park Commission - Rockwood Hall Park - Environmental Impact Study, 1975 (Box 172, Folder 2-3, Box 173, Folder 1)
      - Taconic State Park Commission - Rockwood Hall Park - Leases, 1977-1984 (Box 173, Folder 2)
      - Taconic State Park Commission - Rockwood Hall Park - Memos, 1962-1976 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Parks, 5
      - Parks - A-Z (Box 175, Folder 5)
      - National Recreation and Parks Association (Box 175, Folder 6)
      - Parks Council (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Foreign, 6
      - Foreign - A-Z (Box 177, Folder 1)
      - Brazilian Association for the Preservation of Wildlife (Box 177, Folder 2)
      - National Parks Foundation of Costa Rica (Box 177, Folder 3)
      - World Wildlife Fund (Box 177, Folder 4, Box 178, Folder 1)
      - World Wildlife Fund - Printed Matter (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - World Wildlife Fund - Turks and Caicos Development Trust (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Recreation, 7
      - Recreation - A-Z (Box 178, Folder 4)
      - Equestrian Center (Proposed) (Box 176, Folder 2)
      - National Fitness Foundation (Box 176, Folder 3)
      - United States Seniors Golf Association (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - D-E, 1982-1986; 10; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - D - Miscellaneous (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Defense - A-Z (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Defense - Center for Defense Information (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Defense - Veterans - A-Z (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Defense - Veterans - American Legion (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Defense - Veterans - Navy League of the United States (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Defense - Veterans - Philippine Veterans (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Defense - Project on the Vietnam Generation (Box 180, Folder 2-3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - E - Miscellaneous (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - Economics, 1982-1986; 11; 12.91 Cubic Feet 34 letter document boxes
    - Economics - A-E (Box 181, Folder 1-4)
    - Economics - F-K (Box 182, Folder 1-5)
    - Economics - L-R (Box 183, Folder 1-4)
    - Economics - S-Z (Box 184, Folder 1-2)
    - Alliance for Free Enterprise (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - American Enterprise Institute for Public Research, 1982-1986 (Box 185, Folder 1-4)
    - Brown Lung Association (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - The Business Council (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Business Council for International Understanding (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Business and Professional People for the Public Interest (Box 186, Folder 4-5)
    - Caribbean Basin Initiative (CBI) Coalition (Box 187, Folder 1-2)
    - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities, 1982-1986 (Box 187, Folder 3-4, Box 188, Folder 1-3)
    - Center for Development Policy, 1982-1986 (Box 189, Folder 1-3, Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Coal Employment Coalition (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Community Careers Resource Center (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Corporation for Enterprise Development (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Corporation for Public-Private Ventures (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Council on Economic Priorities (Box 191, Folder 2-4, Box 192, Folder 1-2)
    - Don't Bankrupt Washington Legal Defense Fund (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Employment Research Associates (Box 192, Folder 4, Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Environmentalists for Full Employment (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Foundation on Economic Trends (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Industrial States Policy Center (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Institute for International Economics (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Institute for International Economics - Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 194, Folder 1-2)
    - International Academy of Management (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development (The World Bank) (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - International Institute for Economic Research (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - International Monetary Fund (IMF) (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Henry A. Kissinger Group (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Manhattan Institute for Policy Research, 1985-1986 (Box 195, Folder 5, Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Massachusetts Coalition for Occupational Safety and Health (Box 196, Folder 2-3)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Northeast Midwest Institute (Box 196, Folder 5, Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Project Work (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Rockford Institute (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Trilateral Commission, 1983-1984 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Trilateral Commission - General, 1984 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Trilateral Commission - David Rockefeller Letters 1982, 1982 January-August (Box 198, Folder 1-4)
    - Trilateral Commission - David Rockefeller Letters 1982, 1982 September-December (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission - David Rockefeller Letters 1983, 1983 January-December (Box 199, Folder 2-3)
    - Trilateral Commission - David Rockefeller Letters 1985 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Trilateral Commission - General File 1985 - A-Z (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission 1983-1984 - Comprehensive Review (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Trilateral Commission - Contributions (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Trilateral Commission - Dinners-Luncheons 1983 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Trilateral Commission - Dinners-Luncheons 1984 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission - Dinners-Luncheons 1985 (Box 201, Folder 2-3)
    - Trilateral Commission - Dinners-Luncheons 1985-1986 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission - Finances (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Trilateral Commission - Fundraising 1982 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Trilateral Commission - Fundraising 1983 (Box 202, Folder 4, Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission - Fundraising 1984 (Box 203, Folder 2-4, Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission - Fundraising 1985 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Trilateral Commission - Future of Trialogue, 1984 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Trilateral Commission - Future of the Commission - General, 1984 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission - Meetings - Rome Plenary April 1983, 1983 April (Box 205, Folder 2-3, Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission - Meetings - Executive Committee January 1984, 1984 January (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Trilateral Commission - Meetings - Washington Plenary April 1984, 1984 April (Box 206, Folder 3-4, Box 207, Folder 1-5)
    - Trilateral Commission - Meetings - Executive Committee July 1984, 1984 July (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission - Meetings - Chairmen's Meeting November 1984, 1984 November (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Trilateral Commission - Meetings - Tokyo Plenary April 1985, 1985 April (Box 208, Folder 3-5, Box 209, Folder 1-2)
    - Trilateral Commission - Meetings 1985 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Trilateral Commission - Meetings 1986 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Trilateral Commission - Meetings 1982 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Trilateral Commission - Meetings 1983 (Box 210, Folder 1-2)
    - Trilateral Commission - Meetings 1984 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Trilateral Commission - Membership, 1982-1985 (Box 210, Folder 4-6, Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission - Printed Matter (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Trilateral Commission - David Rockefeller Letters 1984 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Trilateral Commission - Seminar May 1984, 1984 May (Box 211, Folder 4-5)
    - Trilateral Commission - Seminar November 1985, 1985 November (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Business Committee on Jamaica, 1981-1985 (Box 212, Folder 2-4, Box 213, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Business Committee on Jamaica - Members (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Business Committee on Jamaica - Trip - Jamaica, 1982 (Box 213, Folder 3-4)
    - US-USSR Trade and Economic Council, Inc., 1982-1986 (Box 214, Folder 1-5)
    - United States Government - President's Council on Economic Advisors (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - Education, 1982-1986; 12; 40.62 Cubic Feet 102 letter document boxes and 4 legal document boxes
    - Education - A-Z, 1
      - Education - A-C (Box 215, Folder 1-3)
      - Education - D-M (Box 216, Folder 1-4)
      - Education - N-V (Box 217, Folder 1-4)
      - Education - W-Z (Box 218, Folder 1)
      - Academy for Educational Development (Box 218, Folder 2)
      - Horatio Alger Association (Box 218, Folder 3)
      - American Philosophical Society (Box 218, Folder 4)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies (Box 219, Folder 1-2)
      - Center for the Study of Public Policy (Box 219, Folder 3)
      - Center for the Study of Responsive Law (Box 219, Folder 4)
      - Center for Urban Education (Box 220, Folder 1-3, Box 221, Folder 1-2)
      - Earthwatch (Box 221, Folder 3)
      - Esalen Institute (Box 222, Folder 1-4, Box 223, Folder 1)
      - Foundation for Children with Learning Disabilities (Box 223, Folder 2)
      - Buckminster Fuller Institute (Box 223, Folder 3)
      - Fund for Higher Education (in Israel) (Box 223, Folder 4)
      - Global Perspectives in Education, Inc. (Box 224, Folder 1)
      - Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement (Box 224, Folder 2)
      - Greenacre Foundation (Box 224, Folder 3)
      - Highlander Research and Education Center, Inc. (Box 224, Folder 4)
      - Institute for Humanistic Studies (Box 224, Folder 5)
      - Institute for International Education - Programs (Box 225, Folder 1)
      - Institute for Journalism Education (Box 225, Folder 2)
      - Institute for Policy Studies (Box 225, Folder 3-4, Box 226, Folder 1-3)
      - Institute for Policy Studies - Contributions (Box 226, Folder 4, Box 227, Folder 1)
      - International Center for Integrative Studies (ICIS) (Box 227, Folder 2-3)
      - Lindisfarne Association, Inc. (Box 227, Folder 4)
      - International Research and Exchange Board (IREX) (Box 228, Folder 1)
      - Media Access Project (Box 228, Folder 2)
      - A.J. Muste Memorial Institute, 1982 (Box 228, Folder 3)
      - National Committee for Citizens in Education (Box 229, Folder 1)
      - National Geographic (Box 229, Folder 2)
      - National Geographic - A-Z (Box 229, Folder 3)
      - National Geographic - Board of Trustees (Box 229, Folder 4)
      - National Geographic Explorer (Box 229, Folder 5)
      - National Geographic - Printed Material (Box 229, Folder 6)
      - Nautilus International Inc. (Box 230, Folder 1)
      - New Society Educational Foundation (Box 230, Folder 2)
      - Pacific Institute for Public Policy Research (Box 230, Folder 3)
      - Public Media Center (Box 230, Folder 4)
      - Santa Fe Institute (Box 231, Folder 1)
      - Sex Information and Education Council of the United States (SIECUS) (Box 231, Folder 2)
      - Trusteeship Institute, Inc. (Box 231, Folder 3)
      - US-USSR Youth Exchange Program (Box 231, Folder 4)
      - Urban Scientific Educational Research (Box 231, Folder 5, Box 232, Folder 1)
      - Woodlands and Whitewater Institute (Box 232, Folder 2)
      - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Box 232, Folder 3)